[Music]
today is my first official day living in
this apartment alone so i thought why
not document it and take you guys along
with this journey this is something new
and this is something i've never done
before because it's my first time moving
out of my house and living in an actual
home by myself and honestly waking up
this morning felt really weird it was so
quiet and peaceful for once i'm just
gonna be doing my daily stuff today it's
a sunday so i'm just probably gonna do
like random errands i'll bring you guys
along throughout the day of me living
alone and hopefully i don't get murdered
and die i don't have blackout shades and
all of my apartment are windows so it
was bright in the morning at like 6 a.m
so that's when i woke up i'm gonna make
myself some coffee right now
[Music]
let me show you guys my new mirror
what is that noise
like machine broken
i'm gonna die
stop this is scary i didn't make that
noise i'm so confused i'm scared
guys i think my coffee machine's broken
and i'm scared it's making weird noises
i just want to drink coffee
okay let's see if it tastes good
[Music]
oh tastes normal cheers
i'm getting a little hungry so i'm also
gonna make myself a smoothie
and this is what i make myself all every
morning because i get lazy
spinach oat milk
oh no i don't have blueberries
[ __ ]
whatever i'll just make it
[Music]
ugh i don't even have protein powder
whatever this is the only like juice cup
i have it's super tiny but
it's also like 12 p.m right now and i
haven't eaten breakfast yet so
one glass of oatmeal
[Applause]
[Music]
i just realized i don't have bananas or
blueberries or strawberries so this is
just going to be a spinach smoothie and
it's going to taste like [ __ ] but since
i'm already halfway through it
i guess i'm gonna have to drink it i'll
add some honey so that it's not
completely shitty
and somewhat
edible
all right let's see how this tastes like
how do you open this
[Music]
well i didn't know i could [ __ ] up a
smitty but i just did so
there's that
oh [ __ ]
ugh
[Music]
i just finished washing the dishes and
why did that take like half my day
guys it's so cloudy today
[Music]
it's so boomy it's making me feel so
iffy i don't know i don't like this
cloudy weather
hi um can i make an appointment for a
pedicure today
uh what time are you guys available
okay that's fine okay no harder all
right thank you bye
yay
i guess i'm getting my pedicures done it
looks like there's gonna be an
[Music]
tear apocalypse there just like
afternoon croissants strolling over
bridges that were built in renaissance
isn't that what every roman's loving
twenty something woman i'm so puffy oh
my gosh
[Music]
guys i'm back with the cutest freaking
toast ever
i rarely get my pedicures done but i
felt like getting it done today because
it was so gloomy outside and depressing
anyways i'm freaking hungry because i
literally didn't eat anything except for
that disgusting smoothie today so i'm
going to try to make something okay i
have chicken in my fridge and i think
it's going to go bad soon so i want to
make use of it so that i don't throw it
out
um i'm just gonna make a chicken salad
chicken
i'm gonna be honest with you guys i
haven't really made chicken by myself in
a while
so i'm not sure if this is if i'm doing
this right but okay i have my chicken
laid out like this i don't know if this
is too much but i have this extra virgin
olive oil it's really good for your body
spray it all over
it's good enough and of course you have
to season it
and then i got this signature grilling
seasoning i've never tried it before so
we'll see
[Music]
why is it so hard opening bottles
i just want to season my chicken why is
it so hard
[Applause]
why is it so hard for me to just
whatever this is making my nose itchy
i should have preheated my oven first
but i'm preheating it now
i guess we'll just have to wait should i
show you guys my toes meanwhile
yay
i'm a little stressed right now because
i have
something due by the end of today and i
haven't even started it so
it's already dark outside look
[Music]
first night in this apartment alone let
me turn on this light so that it's
not as scary
[Music]
ink i think my chicken's almost ready so
i'm going to prepare my salad right now
look what i have
a customized cutting board this is so
cute
it has hj on it hj is my korean initial
[Music]
these are already pre-washed
[Applause]
[Music]
okay my salad's pretty much ready
i can't wait to eat this i'm so hungry
[Music]
do you guys see this
i broke my nail this morning and today
i'm getting my tv finally yes let's go
pick up my tv from best buy i don't know
how i'm gonna carry the big tv by myself
but
[Music]
oh my gosh i just picked up my tv and
the most traumatic thing literally
happened today when i was walking down
the street i literally got assaulted by
a homeless man or whatever some random
man assaulted me on the sidewalk he
pushed me to like the building wall and
i like my body literally jolted to the
side on the building and like i i'm not
even being dramatic right now i think i
have a bruise right here he like shoved
me anyways that just reminded me i
should go buy myself pepper spray and a
taser gun or something so that i could
keep myself safe
while living alone in the city so yeah
there's that and now i have to set up my
big ass tv getting this thing into my
apartment was literally the most hardest
thing i've ever experienced in my entire
life one thing i realized is there are
so many nice people in new york like 10
different people offered to help and i
was like oh thank you but no thank you
there are some really nice people but
there are also really mean people like
the guy who shoved me against the wall
literally i never thought that that
would ever happen to me but it just did
so i'm kind of in a mental shock right
now but
look at the view look at the sunset
today guys it's so pretty oh why am i so
tired i literally did one thing i
couldn't even buy myself a nail clipper
my nails still broken it looks so ugly
[Music]
why is setting up the tv so hard i don't
get it
[Music]
all right well my tv is finally set up
this looks kind of depressing like it's
so tiny on the floor but the tv stand
didn't come yet so it's gonna be on the
floor for now it looks a little
depressing
[Music]
i could say